Matthew Hope

.NET Developer

Bromley, London, UK +447530240811 matt@matthewhope.co.uk matthewhope.co.uk



SKILLS

Primarily using C# to target .NET Core, I am proficient in creating internet-connected, cloud-enabled applications and solutions which adhere to the principles of Clean Architecture. I have experience in creating secure RESTful Web APIs and I currently run my own website, <a href="mailto:matthewards-matthewards-nath-nath-water-all-nat

- Microsoft Azure
- ASP.NET Core MVC, RESTful API, Razor Pages
- Entity Framework Core, SQL Server
- HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Bootstrap
- Git, GitHub, Agile Methodologies, Clean Architecture

EXPERIENCE

RSPB Bromley Local Group - Website & Social Media Administrator
JANUARY 2020 - PRESENT

Self-Employed, London, UK - .NET Developer

OCTOBER 2019 - PRESENT

NHS Dysart Surgery, Bromley, UK - Administration Officer

MARCH 2019 - MAY 2019

EDUCATION

University of Southampton - *MMath Mathematics (CertHE)*

SEPTEMBER 2016 - NOVEMBER 2018

Trinity School, Croydon

SEPTEMBER 2008 - JULY 2015

- A Levels: Maths (A), Further Maths (A), Spanish (A), Physics (B)
- GCSEs: 10 A* (including Maths, Additional Maths and English), 2 A

QUALIFICATIONS

Microsoft Certified: Azure Developer Associate

FEBRUARY 2020